<Lesson>
    <LessonScreens>
      <LessonScreen>
        <Buttons>
          <Button>
            <ButtonLocationType>NEXT</ButtonLocationType>
            <Text>Continue</Text>
            <Timer></Timer>
            <TransitionType>NEXT_SCREEN</TransitionType>
          </Button>
        </Buttons>
        <Characters>
          <Character>
            <CharacterType>Hero</CharacterType>
            <Timer></Timer>
          </Character>
        </Characters>
        <InformationBoxes>
          <InformationBox>
            <Text>Hey Gooble users welcome to the class</Text>
            <TextType>ALT1</TextType>
            <Timer></Timer>
          </InformationBox>
        </InformationBoxes>
      </LessonScreen>
<LessonScreen>
        <Buttons>
          <Button>
            <ButtonLocationType>NEXT</ButtonLocationType>
            <Text>Continue</Text>
            <Timer></Timer>
            <TransitionType>NEXT_SCREEN</TransitionType>
          </Button>
        </Buttons>
        <Characters>
          <Character>
            <CharacterType>Hero</CharacterType>
            <Timer></Timer>
          </Character>
        </Characters>
        <InformationBoxes>
          <InformationBox>
            <Text>Culture refers to the cumulative deposit of knowledge, experience, beliefs, values, attitudes, meanings, hierarchies, religion, notions of time, roles, spatial relations, concepts of the universe, and material objects and possessions acquired by a group of people in the course of generations through individual and group striving.
Culture is the systems of knowledge shared by a relatively large group of people.
Culture is communication, communication is culture.
Culture in its broadest sense is cultivated behavior; that is the totality of a person's learned, accumulated experience which is socially transmitted, or more briefly, behavior through social learning.
A culture is a way of life of a group of people--the behaviors, beliefs, values, and symbols that they accept, generally without thinking about them, and that are passed along by communication and imitation from one generation to the next.
Culture is symbolic communication. Some of its symbols include a group's skills, knowledge, attitudes, values, and motives. The meanings of the symbols are learned and deliberately perpetuated in a society through its institutions.
		</Text>
            <TextType>ALT1</TextType>
            <Timer></Timer>
          </InformationBox>
        </InformationBoxes>
      </LessonScreen>
<LessonScreen>
        <Buttons>
          <Button>
            <ButtonLocationType>NEXT</ButtonLocationType>
            <Text>Continue</Text>
            <Timer></Timer>
            <TransitionType>NEXT_SCREEN</TransitionType>
          </Button>
        </Buttons>
        <Characters>
          <Character>
            <CharacterType>Hero</CharacterType>
            <Timer></Timer>
          </Character>
        </Characters>
        <InformationBoxes>
          <InformationBox>
            <Text>Culture consists of patterns, explicit and implicit, of and for behavior acquired and transmitted by symbols, constituting the distinctive achievement of human groups, including their embodiments in artifacts; the essential core of culture consists of traditional ideas and especially their attached values; culture systems may, on the one hand, be considered as products of action, on the other hand, as conditioning influences upon further action.
Culture is the sum of total of the learned behavior of a group of people that are generally considered to be the tradition of that people and are transmitted from generation to generation.
Culture is a collective programming of the mind that distinguishes the members of one group or category of people from another.
		</Text>
            <TextType>ALT1</TextType>
            <Timer></Timer>
          </InformationBox>
        </InformationBoxes>
      </LessonScreen>
<LessonScreen>
        <Buttons>
          <Button>
            <ButtonLocationType>NEXT</ButtonLocationType>
            <Text>Continue</Text>
            <Timer></Timer>
            <TransitionType>NEXT_SCREEN</TransitionType>
          </Button>
        </Buttons>
        <Characters>
          <Character>
            <CharacterType>Hero</CharacterType>
            <Timer></Timer>
          </Character>
        </Characters>
        <InformationBoxes>
          <InformationBox>
            <Text>Different cultural groups think, feel, and act differently. There is no scientific standards for considering one group as intrinsically superior or inferior to another. Studying differences in culture among groups and societies presupposes a position of cultural relativism. It does not imply normalcy for oneself, nor for one's society. It, however, calls for judgment when dealing with groups or societies different from one's own. Information about the nature of cultural differences between societies, their roots, and their consequences should precede judgment and action. Negotiation is more likely to succeed when the parties concerned understand the reasons for the differences in viewpoints.
		</Text>
            <TextType>ALT1</TextType>
            <Timer></Timer>
          </InformationBox>
        </InformationBoxes>
      </LessonScreen>
    </LessonScreens>
</Lesson>